(Howard:)...who claims he wrote
Beverly Hills Chihuahua.
Then you give up on love,
go to Marie Callender's...
(Howard:)...buy a pie and eat it in your car
in the parking lot.
- What time should I be at your mother's?
- I told her around 7.
(Leonard:)I swear, that man is the most egotistical,
insufferable human being I have ever met.
(Penny:)Yeah, but you two
make such a cute couple.
Like Bert and Ernie.
(Penny:)You guys even teach me stuff
about words and numbers.
(Leonard:)Well, I've had it, I am done.
I can't live with him one more minute.
Wow, where are you gonna go?
Well, I was thinking here with you.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
Is that a problem?
No, no, no. It's great.
It's terrific. You know, I just can't
help feel bad about Sheldon.
I mean, how's he gonna
get by without you...
...Ernie?